(globalThis.TURBOPACK = globalThis.TURBOPACK || []).push([
  "object" == typeof document ? document.currentScript : void 0,
  {
    679431: (e) => {
      "use strict";
      e.s({ default: () => d }, 679431);
      var n = e.i(731636),
        t = e.i(838653),
        i = e.i(747047);
      let a = function () {
        let e =
            arguments.length > 0 && void 0 !== arguments[0]
              ? arguments[0]
              : 768,
          [n, i] = (0, t.useState)(!1);
        return (
          (0, t.useEffect)(() => {
            let n = () => {
              i(window.innerWidth < e);
            };
            return (
              n(),
              window.addEventListener("resize", n),
              () => window.removeEventListener("resize", n)
            );
          }, [e]),
          n
        );
      };
      var s = e.i(712568),
        o = e.i(12448),
        r = e.i(55157);
      function l(e) {
        let { index: i, question: a, answer: l, open: c, onToggle: d } = e,
          [h, u] = (0, t.useState)(!1);
        (0, t.useEffect)(() => {
          u(c === i);
        }, [c, i]);
        let m = () => {
          d ? d(i) : u(!h);
        };
        return (0, n.jsxs)("div", {
          className: "flex flex-row w-full",
          children: [
            (0, n.jsx)("div", {
              className: "hidden lg:flex items-start mr-1 w-1/12",
              children: (0, n.jsx)("div", {
                className:
                  "bg-white dark:bg-gray-900 rounded-lg shadow-md p-2 border border-gray-200 dark:border-gray-700",
                children: (0, n.jsx)(s.default, {
                  src: "/logo_alpha.webp",
                  className: "rounded-full",
                  alt: "FAQ",
                  width: 150,
                  height: 150,
                }),
              }),
            }),
            (0, n.jsx)("div", {
              className:
                "bg-white dark:bg-[#0B101C] p-4 md:p-6 rounded-lg shadow-md flex flex-row w-full lg:w-11/12 border border-gray-200 dark:border-gray-700",
              children: h
                ? (0, n.jsxs)("div", {
                    className:
                      "flex flex-row items-center justify-between w-full",
                    children: [
                      (0, n.jsxs)("div", {
                        children: [
                          (0, n.jsx)("h3", {
                            className:
                              "text-lg md:text-xl font-semibold mb-4 text-gray-900 dark:text-white",
                            children: a,
                          }),
                          (0, n.jsx)("p", {
                            className: "text-gray-600 dark:text-gray-300",
                            children: l,
                          }),
                        ],
                      }),
                      (0, n.jsx)(o.FontAwesomeIcon, {
                        icon: r.faChevronUp,
                        className:
                          "text-gray-600 dark:text-gray-300 self-end cursor-pointer",
                        size: "lg",
                        onClick: m,
                        role: "button",
                      }),
                    ],
                  })
                : (0, n.jsxs)("div", {
                    className:
                      "flex flex-row items-center justify-between w-full",
                    children: [
                      (0, n.jsx)("h3", {
                        className:
                          "text-base md:text-lg text-gray-900 dark:text-white",
                        children: a,
                      }),
                      (0, n.jsx)(o.FontAwesomeIcon, {
                        icon: r.faChevronDown,
                        className:
                          "text-gray-600 dark:text-gray-300 self-end cursor-pointer",
                        size: "lg",
                        onClick: m,
                        role: "button",
                      }),
                    ],
                  }),
            }),
          ],
        });
      }
      function c() {
        let e = a(),
          [s, o] = (0, t.useState)("General"),
          [r, c] = (0, t.useState)(-1);
        (0, t.useEffect)(() => {
          c(e ? -1 : 0);
        }, [e]);
        let d = (e) => {
          c(r === e ? null : e);
        };
        return (0, n.jsxs)("div", {
          className: "w-full",
          children: [
            (0, n.jsx)("div", {
              className: "flex flex-row justify-center space-x-1 mb-5 w-full",
              children: [
                { id: "General", label: "General" },
                { id: "Presale", label: "Presale" },
                { id: "Dashboard", label: "Dashboard" },
                { id: "Other", label: "Other" },
              ].map((t) =>
                (0, n.jsx)(
                  i.default,
                  {
                    variant: 2,
                    className:
                      "text-xs md:text-sm lg:text-lg sm:mr-2 mr-0 py-2 md:py-4 px-2 md:px-4 lg:px-8 font-bold ".concat(
                        s === t.id
                          ? "bg-purple-600 dark:bg-white dark:text-white text-purple-900"
                          : "text-ethai dark:text-ethai hover:text-purple-700 dark:hover:text-purple-300"
                      ),
                    onClick: () => {
                      var n;
                      return (n = t.id), void (o(n), c(e ? -1 : 0));
                    },
                    children: t.label,
                  },
                  t.id
                )
              ),
            }),
            (0, n.jsxs)("div", {
              className: "flex flex-col justify-between",
              children: [
                (0, n.jsxs)("div", {
                  className: "".concat("General" === s ? "contents" : "hidden"),
                  children: [
                    (0, n.jsx)(l, {
                      index: 0,
                      question:
                        "What is Etherchain AI, and what is the strategic mission behind its development?",
                      answer:
                        "Etherchain AI is a next-generation blockchain ecosystem seamlessly integrated with artificial intelligence. Its core mission is to transform decentralized applications, governance, and infrastructure through groundbreaking innovations such as the Proof of Intelligence (PoI) consensus mechanism, the Artificial Intelligence Virtual Machine (AIVM), and a transparent, verifiable AI execution framework. Etherchain AI is committed to building a smarter, more secure, and equitable decentralized future.",
                      open: r,
                      onToggle: d,
                    }),
                    (0, n.jsx)(l, {
                      index: 1,
                      question:
                        "What distinguishes Etherchain AI's PoI consensus from conventional mechanisms?",
                      answer:
                        "Proof-of-Intelligence (PoI) is a next-generation consensus mechanism that utilizes AI-driven computation to validate transactions. It replaces resource-heavy models with intelligent validation, enhancing network scalability, security, and speedâ€”while significantly reducing energy usage and enabling real-time adaptability within decentralized systems.",
                      open: r,
                      onToggle: d,
                    }),
                    (0, n.jsx)(l, {
                      index: 2,
                      question:
                        "How does the AIVM operate within Etherchain AI's decentralized infrastructure?",
                      answer:
                        "The Artificial Intelligence Virtual Machine (AIVM) serves as a dynamic on-chain execution layer for AI-enhanced decentralized applications. By embedding intelligent computation into the blockchain, it empowers developers to build autonomous, data-responsive dApps with elevated efficiency, scalability, and real-time performance.",
                      open: r,
                      onToggle: d,
                    }),
                    (0, n.jsx)(l, {
                      index: 3,
                      question:
                        "What are the details of the Etherchain AI presale?",
                      answer:
                        "The Etherchain AI presale offers early adopters the opportunity to purchase tokens before the public launch. Participants benefit from discounted prices and exclusive perks, such as governance voting rights and priority access to ecosystem features like the Memecoin Launchpad.",
                      open: r,
                      onToggle: d,
                    }),
                    (0, n.jsx)(l, {
                      index: 4,
                      question:
                        "How is the Etherchain AI presale structured and what should participants know?",
                      answer:
                        "Etherchain AI's Transparent AI Framework embeds auditability and explainability into every layer of AI decision-making. By enforcing verifiable logic and accountable execution, the framework builds trust, empowers developers, and ensures users can confidently engage with AI-driven processes across the ecosystem.",
                      open: r,
                      onToggle: d,
                    }),
                    (0, n.jsx)(l, {
                      index: 5,
                      question:
                        "What is the function of decentralized governance within the Etherchain AI ecosystem?",
                      answer:
                        "Decentralized governance forms the core of Etherchain AI's operational model. ETHAI token holders gain direct influence over protocol evolution by proposing and voting on key initiatives. This community-driven framework ensures alignment with collective values, while AI enhances transparency, efficiency, and responsiveness in governance processes.",
                      open: r,
                      onToggle: d,
                    }),
                  ],
                }),
                (0, n.jsxs)("div", {
                  className: "".concat("Presale" === s ? "block" : "hidden"),
                  children: [
                    (0, n.jsx)(l, {
                      index: 0,
                      question: "What is in the minimum investment?",
                      answer:
                        "There is no minimum investment. You can invest as little as $10.",
                      open: r,
                      onToggle: d,
                    }),
                    (0, n.jsx)(l, {
                      index: 1,
                      question: "When do I receive my ETHAI tokens?",
                      answer:
                        "You will receive your ETHAI tokens instantly into your wallet after each successful purchase â€” no waiting, no manual claiming required. Stay informed about future updates, mainnet deployment, and community developments by following our official social channels and community groups.",
                      open: r,
                      onToggle: d,
                    }),
                    (0, n.jsx)(l, {
                      index: 2,
                      question: "Which cryptocurrencies do you accept?",
                      answer:
                        "During the presale, we accept Ethereum (ETH) and Tether (USDT â€“ ERC-20 standard) as valid payment options. These trusted and widely-used assets ensure a smooth and secure transaction process for all participants.",
                      open: r,
                      onToggle: d,
                    }),
                    (0, n.jsx)(l, {
                      index: 3,
                      question: "When will the presale finish?",
                      answer:
                        "The presale will conclude once the funding target is reached, with a soft cap set at $8 million and a hard cap at $10 million. During this period, we aim to sell a total of 25 million ETHAI tokens. This structure ensures a swift and efficient launch while maintaining strong early momentum and strategic capital allocation.",
                      open: r,
                      onToggle: d,
                    }),
                    (0, n.jsx)(l, {
                      index: 4,
                      question: "Where can I sell my ETHAI tokens?",
                      answer:
                        "After the presale concludes, ETHAI will be officially listed on Bybit and OKX, two of the leading global cryptocurrency exchanges. Once listed, you'll be able to view and trade your tokens directly on these platforms with full transparency and liquidity.",
                      open: r,
                      onToggle: d,
                    }),
                    (0, n.jsx)(l, {
                      index: 5,
                      question:
                        "Which exchanges will ETHAI tokens be listed on?",
                      answer:
                        "Following the presale, ETHAI will be listed on top-tier centralized exchanges, including Bybit and OKX. These listings will provide global exposure, deep liquidity, and secure trading environments for all token holders.",
                      open: r,
                      onToggle: d,
                    }),
                  ],
                }),
                (0, n.jsxs)("div", {
                  className: "".concat("Dashboard" === s ? "block" : "hidden"),
                  children: [
                    (0, n.jsx)(l, {
                      index: 0,
                      question:
                        "How can I see how many tokens I have purchased?",
                      answer:
                        "You can view your purchased tokens by connecting your wallet to the site and accessing your personal dashboard. All your holdings and transaction history will be displayed securely in one place.  ",
                      open: r,
                      onToggle: d,
                    }),
                    (0, n.jsx)(l, {
                      index: 1,
                      question: "Can I stake my ETHAI tokens?",
                      answer:
                        "Staking will be available after the mainnet launch and presale conclusion. By staking your ETHAI tokens, you'll be able to earn rewards ranging from 4% to 18%, depending on the amount you hold.",
                      open: r,
                      onToggle: d,
                    }),
                  ],
                }),
                (0, n.jsxs)("div", {
                  className: "".concat("Other" === s ? "block" : "hidden"),
                  children: [
                    (0, n.jsx)(l, {
                      index: 0,
                      question: "How do I contact the EtherChainAI team?",
                      answer:
                        "You can reach the Etherchain AI team directly through our official Telegram Support Channel or via email at support@etherchain.ai.",
                      open: r,
                      onToggle: d,
                    }),
                    (0, n.jsx)(l, {
                      index: 1,
                      question: "How can i enter the $250,000 giveaway?",
                      answer:
                        "You can secure your access by completing all the required tasks outlined in the participation process. This ensures fair entry and verifies genuine community engagement.",
                      open: r,
                      onToggle: d,
                    }),
                  ],
                }),
              ],
            }),
          ],
        });
      }
      function d() {
        return (0, n.jsx)("section", {
          id: "faq",
          className: "relative py-20 bg-white dark:bg-gray-950 min-h-[75vh]",
          children: (0, n.jsxs)("div", {
            className:
              "relative z-10 w-[95%] max-w-4xl mx-auto px-4 sm:px-6 lg:px-8",
            children: [
              (0, n.jsxs)("div", {
                className: "text-center mb-16",
                children: [
                  (0, n.jsx)("h2", {
                    className:
                      "text-[16px] font-semibold text-ethai dark:text-ethai mb-2 uppercase tracking-wide",
                    children: "FAQ",
                  }),
                  (0, n.jsx)("h3", {
                    className:
                      "text-3xl md:text-4xl font-bold text-gray-900 dark:text-white mb-6",
                    children: "Frequently Asked Questions",
                  }),
                ],
              }),
              (0, n.jsx)(c, { className: "z-[2]" }),
            ],
          }),
        });
      }
    },
    829128: (e) => {
      e.n(e.i(679431));
    },
  },
]);

//# sourceMappingURL=97824e063cddd7eb.js.map
